[22] Found DOI: 10.4490/algae.2018.33.3.6 - Title: Revisiting the Parvilucifera infectans / P. sinerae (Alveolata, Perkinsozoa) species complex, two parasitoids of dinoflagellates
[23] Found DOI: 10.1111/j.1550-7408.2001.tb00207.x - Title: FISH Probes for the Detection of the Parasitic Dinoflagellate <i>Amoebophrya</i> sp. Infecting the Dinoflagellate <i>Akashiwo sanguinea</i> in Chesapeake Bay
[24] Found DOI: 10.4490/algae.2017.32.7.28 - Title: Morphological observations and phylogenetic position of the parasitoid nanoflagellate Pseudopirsonia sp. (Cercozoa) infecting the marine diatom Coscinodiscus wailesii (Bacillariophyta)
[28] Found DOI: 10.11626/kjeb.2021.39.4.573 - Title: New records of five taxa of unarmored and thin-walled dinoflagellates from brackish and coastal waters of Korea
[29] Found DOI: 10.7850/jkso.2015.20.3.151 - Title: Semi-daily Variations in Populations of the Dinoflagellates Dinophysis acuminata and Oxyphysis oxytoxoides and a Mixotrophic Ciliate Prey Mesodinium rubrum in Masan Bay
[31] Found DOI: 10.1016/j.hal.2015.02.001 - Title: Phased cell division and facultative mixotrophy of the marine dinoflagellate Fragilidium duplocampanaeforme and its trophic interactions with the dinoflagellates Dinophysis spp. and a ciliate Mesodinium rubrum
[32] Found DOI: 10.1021/pr0499186.s003 - Title: Proteome Analysis of Tobacco Bright Yellow-2 (BY-2) Cell Culture Plastids  as a Model for Undifferentiated Heterotrophic Plastids
[33] Found DOI: 10.3354/meps160027 - Title: Lethal effect of the dinoflagellate Heterocapsa circularisquama upon the tintinnid ciliate Favella taraikaensis
[34] Error: 'cp949' codec can't encode character '\u2010' in position 81: illegal multibyte sequence
[35] Found DOI: 10.1016/j.hal.2019.101633 - Title: Distribution and genetic diversity of the parasitic dinoflagellate Amoebophrya in coastal waters of China
[38] Found DOI: 10.1101/2025.05.13.653706 - Title: From Red Tides to Healthy Ecosystems by Nutrient Management in Ise Bay and Mikawa Bay
[39] Found DOI: 10.1128/aem.06678-11 - Title: Molecular Diversity of the Syndinean Genus Euduboscquella Based on Single-Cell PCR Analysis
[40] Found DOI: 10.1093/molbev/msq332 - Title: Dynamics of Actin Evolution in Dinoflagellates
[41] Found DOI: 10.3354/ame01474 - Title: Feeding behavior, spatial distribution and phylogenetic affinities of the heterotrophic dinoflagellate Oxyphysis oxytoxoides
[42] Found DOI: 10.1007/978-3-662-11340-0_6 - Title: Ciliates (Phylum: Ciliophora)
[43] Found DOI: 10.1111/j.1529-8817.2009.00777.x - Title: DOES<i>DINOPHYSIS CAUDATA</i>(DINOPHYCEAE) HAVE PERMANENT PLASTIDS?
[44] Found DOI: 10.3410/f.1053807.505743 - Title: Faculty Opinions recommendation of First successful culture of the marine dinoflagellate Dinophysis acuminata.
